原创翻译  双语字幕
《超女》前情提要
Previously on Supergirl...
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
总统一直在帮莱克斯·卢瑟
The President's been working for Lex Luthor.
莱克斯有坦克
Lex has a tank.
-坦克  坦克  坦克  -好了
- Tank. Tank. Tank. - All right. All right,
翻译     DustD  洗七里  DerbyNinja
坦克  坦克  坦克  坦克
Tank. Tank. Tank. Tank. Tank.
是超女
It's Supergirl.
莱克斯称之为Ryzhaya Dch
Lexie calls her Ryzhaya Dch.
是"红色之女"的意思
That's "Red Daughter."
翻译     阿p  左左  C·A
莱克斯教导她去痛恨美国
Lex has taught her to hate America.
莱克斯让卡兹尼亚入侵美国  背叛他们
Lex convinces Kaznia to invade the US, betrays them--
校对     肉松  饿得慌
然后他自己去阻止
And maybe he stops it himself.
你们重启了我
You rebooted me.
我不准备放你走
I'm not going to release you.
你得穿过传送门  你一到了另一边
Go through the portal. Once you're on the other side,
时间轴    想念Gallifrey的Wholock  三水
告知我位置  我们会解救营地
inform me of the location, and we'll liberate the camp.
-开始提取  -不
- Starting extraction. - No!
后期     你是不是饿得慌
我们不知道会发生什么  我需要我的超能力
We don't know what's coming. I need my strength.
-你不稳定  -那就让我稳定
- But you're unstable. - Then stabilize me!
总监     你是不是饿得慌
我都记起来了
I remember.
卡拉  你不能走
Kara, you can't go!
我在这
I'm here.
我非常想你
I've missed you so much.
入侵我们国家的
...an invasion of our country
和危险的国家卡兹尼亚
by the dangerous rogue state of Kaznia...
单枪匹马挫败了侵略者  杀死了恐怖分子
One man thwarted the invaders and killed the terrorist.
卢瑟先生  一个懂得感恩的国家谢谢你
Mr. Luthor, a grateful nation thanks you.
怎么会这样
How did this happen?
24小时前
华盛顿特区
卡拉·丹弗斯跑掉了
Kara Danvers got away.
我让你失望了
I failed you.
红色之女
Oh, Ryzhaya Dch,
你永远不会让我失望
you could never fail me.
你让我去杀了她
You asked me to kill her.
你让她流血了
You made her bleed.
让她走下神坛
但依然  我应该想到
But still, I should have known
只有氪石是杀不死卡拉·丹弗斯的
Kryptonite alone could never kill Kara Danvers.
不过  她的内心
Her heart, however,
让她软弱到连氪石都无法使之达到的程度
makes her weaker than Kryptonite ever could.
去把这项任务执行到底吧
Go and finish what we started.
美国将会跪在我们脚下
超 女
第四季 第二十二集[本季终]
阿美特克能源提炼厂 6小时前
求你  求你不要
Please. Please don't...
别担心  不会痛的
Don't worry. It won't hurt.
不要
No...
看来我弄错了
Guess I was wrong.
外星能量传输完毕
Alien energy transfer complete.
你的手套应该充上能了
Your gauntlet should be charged.
只有一个办法可以知道
Only one way to find out.
打扰一下  站着别动
Excuse me, uh, stand very still.
去拿拖布
Get a mop.
我不是让你下次不要畏缩吗
Didn't we talk about flinching?
不不不  是奥蒂斯  他又死了
No. No, no, it's Otis. He's dead, again.
洛克伍德
Lockwood.
我最恨的就是
There's nothing I hate more
一个有勇气实现自己信念的人
than a man with the courage of his convictions.
还拥有与之匹配的超能力
With the superpowers to match them.
现在他已经没用了  我们应该除掉他
Now that he's served his usefulness, we should take care of him.
派一支小队去解决  只选你信任的人
Send a team to do it. Only people you trust.
好的  卢瑟先生
Yes, Mr. Luthor.
伊芙
Eve?
这个国家  这个星球
This country, this planet...
马上就要是我们的了  你能感受到吗
It's nearly ours. Can you feel it?
自从遇到你之后就一直能
Ever since the moment I met you.
卫星图像确认
Satellite images confirm
海外正在集结卡兹尼亚军队
a Kaznian force is amassing off the coast.
白宫 1小时前
我倒不是不相信这个计划
Not that I don't trust the plan,
但你确定我不用去地堡里吗
but are you sure I shouldn't be in a bunker somewhere?
你曾是个坐冷板凳  毫无前途的议员
You were a backbench, backwater senator.
然后我搞定了马斯丁的竞选伙伴
Then I took out Marsdin's running mate
让你成了副总统候选人
and got you on the ticket.
然后我还让马斯丁下了台
Then I brought down Marsdin, as well.
我弹指之间让你从无名小卒成为了总统先生
From zero to Mr. President with the snap of my fingers.
你真的想问我对这件事是否有把握吗
Are you seriously asking me if I'm sure about something?
我到如今应该学会了
I should have learned by now,
绝不要质疑莱克斯·卢瑟
never doubt Lex Luthor.
放轻松  菲利
Relax, Phil.
很快  超女就会死
Soon, Supergirl will be dead.
而你将成为美国人挚爱的
And you will be America's beloved,
胜利的战时总统
victorious wartime president.
拥有比历代共和国总统
With more allegiances and more power
更多的同盟与能力
than any president in the history of the republic.
好吧  敬此一杯
Well, cheers to that.
卢瑟先生
是时候了吗
是的  我的朋友
祝好运
为了上帝
为了卡兹尼亚
为了卢瑟先生
进攻
* 如今  结局将至
And now, the end is near *
* 我将面临人生的最后落幕
And so I face the final curtain *
* 吾友  我将言无不尽
My friend I'll say it clear *
* 我将述说我所铭记的经历
I'll state my case of which I'm certain *
开火
* 我度过了充实的一生
I've lived a life that's full *
* 我走过了每一条道路
I've traveled each and every highway *
* 但  远不止如此
And more, much more than this *
* 还是用我自己的方式
I did it my way *
* 男人究竟是什么
For what is a man *
* 他拥有什么
What has he got? *
这是什么意思
* 唯有其身  别无他物
If not himself then he has naught *
* 这样直言不讳地畅所欲言
To say the things he truly feels *
* 抛弃那些谄媚虚伪的字眼
And not the words of one who kneels *
* 时间证明  我经受住了磨难
The record shows I took the blows *
* 用我自己的方式
And did it my way! *
不  不
No. No!
超女已经死了
Supergirl is dead.
发生了什么
What happened?
卡兹尼亚人入侵了
The Kaznians invaded.
你的信号迟了  我本该领军袭击的
Your signal was late. I was supposed to lead the attack.
不  红色之女  你做了你应该做的事
No, Ryzhaya Dch. You did exactly what you were meant to do.
你背叛了我
You betrayed me.
背叛了卡兹尼亚
Betrayed Kaznia.
我能怎么说  我为身为美国人而自豪
What can I say? I'm proud to be an American.
白宫有突发新闻
We have breaking news coming out the White House.
莱克斯·卢瑟
Lex Luthor...
米德维尔  现今
我必须阻止他
I have to stop him.
卡拉  你差点丧命
Kara, you barely escaped with your life.
他还有能杀死红色之女的武器
And he has a weapon that killed Red Daughter.
他在卡兹尼亚时在她身上做试验
He did experiments on her in Kaznia.
他知道如何打倒她
He knew how to take her down,
但他仍需要靠红色之女来杀我
but he still needed Red Daughter to kill me.
你差点就死了
You basically died.
但我幸存了下来
But I survived.
莱克斯不知道这点  这是我的优势
And Lex doesn't know that. That's to my advantage.
莱克斯和总统成功说服大众
Lex and the President have succeeded in convincing the people
所有的外星人都是危险的
that all aliens are dangerous.
-超女是公众之敌  -莱克斯是英雄
- That Supergirl is the enemy. - And Lex is the hero.
看来我有责任让他们看清菜克斯的真面目
Well, I guess it's my job to show them who Lex really is.
让他们看清真相
Show them the truth.
我只是害怕人们不肯听
I just fear that the people won't listen.
不  我不会让恐惧胜利
No, I will not let fear win.
和我姐姐并肩作战
And with my sister by my side,
一切皆有可能
anything is possible.
艾美特克能量提炼厂
红色之女
Ryzhaya Dch.
我信任过你  艾丽克斯
I trusted you, Alex.
你要么是傻  要么是天真得惊人
You're either dumb or staggeringly naive.
你可以随意调查我的历史  可以上网
You had my history at your disposal. Internet accessible.
哪怕你愿意看上一眼  也会发现两件事
If you had bothered to look, you'd have realized two things.
维护穷苦破碎的卡兹尼亚
Defending poor, broken Kaznia
对莱克斯·卢瑟根本不值一提
is a little small potatoes for Lex Luthor.
但或许更值得注意的是
But, perhaps more significantly,
我恨氪星人
I hate Kryptonians.
而你是什么  氪星人
And what are you? A Kryptonian.
你该让我去死
You should've let me die.
死  我对你有更大的计划
Die? I have bigger plans for you.
洛克伍德炼钢厂
奥蒂斯·格雷夫斯身亡
Otis Graves was found dead.
他的尸体旁有一份宣言
Next to his body was a manifesto,
承认卢瑟先生的所有罪行都是他所为
taking detailed credit for all of Mr. Luthor's crimes.
鉴于这个新证据  我赦免了卢瑟先生
In light of this new evidence, I have pardoned Mr. Luthor.
我任命他为新任外星事务部部长
I am appointing him the new Secretary of Alien Affairs.
因为他今天的英勇行为
Because of his heroics today...
他知识渊博  了解关于外星人的一切
...profound knowledge of everything alien.
卢瑟先生向你问好
Mr. Luthor sends his regards.
问好  问好  问好
Regards, regards, regards,
问好  问好  问好  问好
regards, regards, regards, regards,
regards, regards, regards, regards, regar...
抱歉  抱歉
Sorry, sorry...
莱克斯·卢瑟利用了我一整年
Lex Luthor has been using me for a year.
为什么
Why?
艾美特克能量提炼厂
我从没见过这种地方
I've never seen anything like this.
尽快习惯  蠢货
Get used to it, stupid.
卢瑟先生的提炼厂需要制造设备
Mr. Luthor needs stuff built for his refinery.
现在你可以开始工作了
Now you can get to work.
哪怕摘掉超能力抑制手铐
Even without the dampening cuffs,
也不能用能力
no powers.
雪莱岛
雪莱岛  这地方四周都是能力抑制塔
Shelley Island. The place is surrounded by power-dampening pylons.
没有能力
Without my powers,
我没办法告诉布莱尼我们的位置
there's no way I can send Brainy our location.
也许他在抛弃我们之前该想到这一点
Maybe he should've thought of that before abandoning us,
那个讲逻辑的白痴
like a logical idiot.
我也生他的气  但我们还有彼此
Look, I'm not happy with him, either. But there are two of us.
声东击西
A diversion?
快点  过去
Move it! Get over here!
老艾
Al.
假如你们要声东击西
If you're going for a diversion,
算上我和我朋友们
count me and my friends in.
我们一直在等人带领我们逃出去
We've been waiting for someone to lead us out of here.
我该猜到会是你  荣恩·荣兹
I should have predicted it would be you, J'onn J'onzz.
他又一次惊人地展示了他的慷慨
In yet another stunning display of magnanimity,
莱克斯·卢瑟捐赠了一种能源
Lex Luthor has donated an energy source
以帮助恢复电力
to help restore electricity
帮助因卡兹尼亚对海岸电网的轰炸
to the thousands of homes that were affected
生活受到影响的数千个家庭
by Kaznia's bombing of the coast's power grid.
总统将宣誓
The President will swear
莱克斯·卢瑟任职外星事务部部长
Lex Luthor in as Secretary of Alien Affairs
仪式将于今天下午在玫瑰园进行
in a Rose Garden ceremony scheduled for later this afternoon.
卡拉
Kara.
我好担心
I was worried.
我听说总统试图封你的口
I heard the President tried to silence you.
我没事
I'm okay.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
超女怎么样了
And then, Supergirl?
她还活着  准备好战斗了
She's alive, and she's ready to fight.
布莱尼  总统命令秘密特工
Brainy, the President had the Secret Service
清空了凯特科所有的服务器
wipe all of CatCo's servers,
我所有的证据都没了  你能恢复吗
and I lost all of my evidence. Can you recover it?
已经恢复好了
It's already done.
太好了  太好了
Yes. Yes!
这能证明莱克斯一直在和卡兹尼亚连手
This proves that Lex has been working with Kaznia,
以及他利用红色之女袭击白宫
and he used Red Daughter to attack the White House.
还能证明政府将超查部废弃设施的外星囚犯
It also proves that the government gave Lex alien prisoners
提供给莱克斯
from the DEO desert facility.
不只是超查部废弃设施的外星人
Not just the aliens from the DEO facility.
荣恩·荣兹  梦想者和我
J'onn J'onzz, Dreamer, and I
发现莱克斯一直在转移
have discovered that Lex has been transferring aliens
被洛克伍德围捕的外星人
rounded up by Ben Lockwood
将他们送到某私人设施
and bringing them to a private facility,
抽取他们的能力
where he's been siphoning their powers.
我的天
My God!
那这个设施在哪
Well, where is this facility?
我们即将获得这个信息
That information is forthcoming.
荣恩和梦想者此刻就在那吗
Is that where J'onn and Dreamer are?
希望如此  他们被绑架了
Hopefully. They have been abducted.
-什么  -你为什么没告诉我们
- What? - Why didn't you tell us that?
你是认真的吗
Are you serious?
对于这么无关紧要的细节
That is a rather strong emotional reaction
你们的反应还真是强烈
for such an insignificant detail.
我们的计划是要拯救外星人
Our plan is to save the aliens.
那些外星人只包括荣恩和梦想者
Those aliens will simply include J'onn and Dreamer.
打扰一下  卢瑟女士  这是给你的
Excuse me, Ms. Luthor, this came for you.
谢谢
Thank you.
是什么
What is it?
莱克斯邀请我去白宫的邀请函
It's an invitation to the White House from Lex.
莉娜  你不是想要去吧
Lena, you can't possibly be thinking of going.
如果我不去  莱克斯就会对付我在乎的人
If I don't go, Lex'll come after the people I care about,
我不能让这种事发生
and I can't have that happen.
而且  如果我见到莱克斯
Besides, if I see Lex,
我就能替我的好朋友拿到一手数据
I'll be able to get some stellar quotes for my best friend's article.
说到这个  卡拉  你最好开始写文章了
Speaking of which, Kara, you better start typing.
母亲
Mother.
莉娜
Lena.
你能相信吗  妹妹
Can you believe it, sis?
卢瑟家的三人都在总统办公室里
Three Luthors in the Oval Office.
只有在美国才会发生
Only in America.
我猜猜
Let me guess,
你把总统绑在条约厅里
you're having the President tied up in the Treaty Room?
傀儡不需要被绑起来  莉娜
Puppets don't need to be tied up, Lena.
只要用细线把他们吊起来就行了
You just hang them up by their strings.
那你为什么不给总统戴个金色假发
Well, why don't you put a blond wig on the President,
你可以把他和伊芙配成一对卖掉
and you can sell him and Eve as a matching set?
好了  你们俩别吵
Now, now. You two play nicely.
这么久以来我们第一次家庭聚会
This is the first family gathering we've had in ages,
我要享受一下
and I'd like to enjoy myself.
你那杀人不眨眼的儿子欺骗了全世界
Your murderous son has duped the world
让大家以为他是地球的英雄
into thinking he's Earth's hero.
这可不是感恩节晚餐
This is hardly Thanksgiving dinner.
对我们家来说  这再正常不过了
Sounds perfectly normal for our family.
不如我们边喝杯茶
Why don't we have a cup of tea
边听莱克斯说说他叫我们来有什么事吧
while Lex tells us why he summoned us here?
他叫我们来是为了炫耀
He summoned us here to gloat.
你把我想得太肤浅了  莉娜  这很伤人
You think so little of me, Lena. It hurts.
我是个多愁善感的人
I'm a sentimental guy.
我做这些不都是为了我自己
I didn't do all of this for me,
是为了我们
I did it for us.
我们都知道如果我想让你们俩死
I mean, look, we all know if I wanted you two dead,
你们不会出现在总统办公室里
you wouldn't be treading on the presidential seal
开茶会了
having a tea party.
我所做的每一件事都是有战略性的
Everything I've done has been strategic
都是为了这一刻的到来
to lead up to this very moment.
卢瑟之名得到平反
The Luthor name cleared.
我们的家族将在历史上占得应有的地位
Our family poised to take its rightful place in history.
那我们应该占得什么样的地位
And what exactly are we poised to do?
彻底改变全球能源
Revolutionize energy worldwide.
我在收集外星人
I'm rounding up aliens
利用他们的超能力来被使用和售卖
and harnessing their power to be used and sold,
有点像超动力的一次性电池
sort of like supercharged disposable batteries.
-太卑鄙了  -卑鄙却可行
- That's vile. - Vile and viable.
正如另一个世界的领袖曾经说过
As another world leader once said,
我不明白人类为什么不该像大自然一样残忍
"I don't see why men shouldn't be as cruel as nature."
不要公开引用希特勒的话  亲爱的
Try not to quote Hitler in public, dear.
这有损我们家族声誉
It'll hurt the brand.
你杀了超人的堂姐  占领了整个国家
You killed Superman's cousin, took over the country...
你凭什么认为他会在阿尔戈坐视不管
What makes you think he's gonna sit idly by on Argo
任由此事发生
and allow this to happen?
我正希望你提到昨日之人
I was hoping you'd bring up The Man of Yesterday.
第一批耗尽的外星人
The first batch of depleted aliens
将会为卫星武器补给能源
will charge the satellite weapon
这样阿尔戈就会变成燃烧的地狱
that will turn Argo into a blazing inferno,
超人就会化为灰烬
and Superman into, well, ash.
我能单独和你说两句吗
May I speak with you privately?
失陪一下
Excuse me for a moment.
请慢慢观赏南草坪的风光
Please enjoy the view of the South Lawn,
它可是以复活节滚彩蛋比赛而出名
famous for its egg-rolling contest.
你不会相信他的鬼话吧  母亲
You're not buying this, Mother?
当然不相信  我已经在他的茶里下了毒
Of course not. I've already poisoned his tea.
如果他不说这么多废话  喝一口茶的话
If he'd stopped running his mouth long enough to take a sip,
他早就死了
he'd be dead by now.
我们从来没讨论过超人  计划不是这样的
We never discussed Superman. This was not the plan.
计划一直都是这样  我只是没通知你们而已
This was always the plan. I just didn't apprise you of it.
你怎么能不通知我  我是你的搭档
How could you not apprise me? I'm your partner.
不是搭档  泰斯马克女士
Not partner, Miss Tessmacher.
女门徒  打杂  仆人
Protegee, factotum, flunky.
我才是做决定的人  明白了吗
I am the decider. Is that clear?
我们的计划是终身能源供应
Our plan was to have a lifetime supply of energy.
你攻击阿尔戈就会浪费一半的能源
You'll waste half of that attacking Argo.
别因为执着于超人而丢弃一切
Don't throw everything away over this obsession with Superman--
我会亲手毁掉超人
Superman will be destroyed by my hand.
他会被烧死
He will burn.
拜托  亲爱的  你会很喜欢的
Come on, honey. You're gonna love it.
我们的胜利值得庆祝
Our victory deserves fireworks.
在这里没法工作
Can't work in here, man.
眼睛看路  兄弟
Hey, man, watch where you're going, brother.
-不  是你推我的  -是你撞到我
- No, no, you shoved me. - You bumped into me, man.
-你在跟谁叫嚣  -给我走开
- Who you talking to? - Back off, man!
住手  不然就进太空舱
Stop it, or you're going to the pods.
好吧
All right, man.
桥塔控制在这里
There's the pylon control.
系统下线
我的超能力回来了
My powers are coming back.
把星体投射到布莱尼和其他人
Astral project to Brainy and the others.
我的报道写得怎么样
Well, how was my article?
太有历史性了
This is historic.
人们会谈论这篇报道
Okay, people are gonna be talking about this article
就像他们当年谈论待伍德沃德和伯恩斯坦一样
like they did with Woodward and Bernstein.
揭穿水门事件丑闻的两名《华盛顿邮报》记者
我不在乎他们是否谈论这篇报道
I don't care if they're talking about it,
只要他们去听就行了
as long as they listen to it.
任务执行完毕
Task executed.
莉莉安·卢瑟的提取装置已经启动
Lillian Luthor's extraction device is now mobilized.
只要我们遇到本·洛克伍德
We can use it to extract the Harun-El from Ben Lockwood's system
我们随时都可以用它从他体内提取哈伦·艾尔
whenever and wherever we encounter him.
然后我就能利用它从詹姆斯体内做提取了
Well, then we can use it to extract from James.
但是首先
But first...
时间就是现在
The time is exactly... now.
各位  莱克斯的外星人能源工厂在雪莱岛
Guys, Lex's alien power facility is at Shelley Island.
时间就是现在是什么意思
What do you mean, "The time is now"?
-各位  -如果我的计算没错
- Guys... - If my calculations are correct,
梦想者刚刚将星体投射到这间办公室
Dreamer has just astral projected into this office.
你料到我会来这吗
You anticipated me being here?
她来了  此时此刻她在想
She is here. She is wondering in this exact moment
她要如何与我们取得联系
how she can contact us.
因为星体投射者
Because an astral projectee
可以将自身送往任何环境中
can place themselves in any environment,
但他们却不能与那里进行任何交流
but they cannot interact with that environment.
那这算什么好计划
So how is this a good plan?
谢谢
Thank you.
梦想者的星体投射是纯梦境能量
Dreamer's astral projection is pure dream energy,
因此  她虽然不能与我们交流
and as such, while she cannot interact with us,
却可以与其他能量作用  使其离子化
she can interact and ionize other energy.
确切来说是电子化
Electrons to be exact.
梦想者  将你的能量
Dreamer, concentrate your energy
聚集在这些水蒸气的分子上
on the molecules in this water vapor,
使其离子化
and ionize it.
我觉得他的意思是在上面写字
I think he means to write on it.
雪莱
雪莱岛
雪莱岛  原来如此
Shelley Island. Of course.
他们有麻烦了
They're in trouble.
我去找詹姆斯
I'll go get James.
好想念这种感觉
I really missed that.
让我们举杯
And now, a toast...
共同庆祝钢铁之躯的毁灭
to incinerating the Man of Steel.
我保证  里面绝对没有钋210
I promise, there's no Polonium-210 in it,
虽然你加在我茶里了
like you put in my tea.
用电离辐射杀死自己的亲生儿子
Killing your own son with ionizing radiation,
真符合你的性格
now that is on brand.
癌症也许让你早衰了
Cancer may have aged you prematurely,
但你犀利不减当年
but you're still as sharp as ever.
所以
So,
你为什么不直接开枪打死我和你妹妹
what's stopping you from shooting me and your sister?
也许我很疯狂  但我对亲人比较偏爱
Call me crazy, but I'm partial to my relatives.
我不忍心杀你们
I just can't bear killing you guys.
你这么做就是弑亲
If you do this, it's genocide.
公众会发现真相  等到那时候...
The public will find out the truth, and when they do--
真相毫无意义
The truth is meaningless.
地球人坚信我是他们的救星
The people of Earth believe I am their savior.
他们需要一个人类英雄  我满足了这个需求
They needed a human hero, and I fulfill that need.
他们的想法永远不会改变
Nothing will ever change their minds.
莱克斯·卢瑟分裂并背叛美国的手段
事实并不重要
Facts are irrelevant.
莱克斯·卢瑟分裂并背叛美国的手段
重要的是宣传方式
All that matters is spin.
人们太蠢了  蠢到不会阅读
People are so stupid, they don't even read.
莱克斯·卢瑟万岁
就算在阅读的时候  也绝对不会思考
And even when they do, they certainly don't think.
莱克斯·卢瑟分裂并背叛美国的手段
我现在是这个国家的领导者
I am the leader of this nation now,
没有任何事能阻止我
and nothing can stop me.
干杯
Toast.
电缆塔坏了
The pylons are off.
荣恩和梦想者在哪里
Where are J'onn and Dreamer?
他们似乎陷入了一场暴乱
It appears they're in the middle of a riot.
更糟的是  这个工厂收集到的外星能量
What's worse, the alien power being collected in this factory,
将被莱克斯用来发射到克莱莫卫星上
Lex has it set up to be discharged into a Claymore satellite.
克莱莫  不是已经被我毁了吗
Claymore? I... I destroyed that.
这似乎是更新更大更强的克莱莫
This appears to be a newer, bigger, better Claymore.
能看出来目标在哪里吗
Can you tell where it's targeting?
目标在太空深处  阿尔戈市
The target is in deep space. Argo City.
他要毁灭我的家人
He's going to wipe out my family.
我也许可以黑进能源中心阻止这一切
I may be able to hack into the power core to stop it.
好  你试试看  我们去救荣恩和梦想者
Good, do that. We'll help J'onn and Dreamer.
超女
Supergirl!
我和我超强伙伴的目的是对付卢瑟
Me and my supercharged friends came here to deal with Luthor
还有他带来的危险外星人
and the dangerous aliens that he brought here.
但是你也来了
But I'm so glad
我很欣慰
you came here too.
这里一定是核心了
This must be the core.
荣恩  梦想者  我的计划成功了
J'onn, Dreamer. My plan worked.
这是抛弃我们的惩罚
That was for abandoning us.
我们来救这些人吧
Now let's help these people.
我会的
I will.
首先  我们有更紧急的事
First, there are more pressing matters.
阿尔戈已经被莱克斯当成了目标
Argo is being targeted by Lex imminently,
只能靠我来阻止
and it is up to me to stop it.
系统拒绝了我的访问
The system is denying me access.
我们应该能做些什么阻止发射
There must be something we can do to stop the launch.
不  我们什么都做不了
No. There is nothing we can do.
能量核已经达到了最高容纳值
The power core has reached its peak capacity.
克莱莫在两分钟内就会向阿尔戈开火
The Claymore will fire on Argo in less than two minutes.
你说核心到达了最高值
You said the core was peaking.
也就是说可能会出现过载对吗
That means it can be overloaded, right?
在我们所剩的时间里  要想让它过载
You would need a power supply of at least 20 pods
至少需要20个太空舱的能量才行
to overload the core in the time we have left.
你准备打算
You're going to try to use
用心理能量让核心过载
your psychic powers to overload the core.
我告诉过你  肯定有办法
I told you there was a way.
这种尝试只有18%的成功率
There is only an 18% chance that this attempt will succeed,
但是这个过程害死你的可能性却有98%
yet a 98% chance that the effort will kill you.
我自己的星球爆发战争时
During the battle for my own home planet,
我跑了  死了百万人
I ran, millions died.
我不会再犯那样的错误
I will not make that same mistake again!
我们来看看效果吧  如何
Now, on with the show. Shall we?
泰斯马克女士
Miss Tessmacher!
为什么卫星没有发动攻击
Why is the satellite not firing?
雪莱岛出了点问题
There's an issue at Shelley Island.
谁都不许走
No one leaves!
别动歪脑筋
Don't get any ideas.
你个小叛徒
You wretched little traitor.
真是我的好女儿
That's my girl.
你流血了
You're bleeding.
我没事
I'm okay.
我们得立刻从本身体里取出哈伦·艾尔
We need to get the Harun-El out of Ben now!
莱克斯
Lex.
去吧  我们来处理
Go. We got this.
你怎么还活着
How are you alive?
你怎么做到的
How did you do it?
你觉得我是怎么做到的
How do you think I did it?
我是超女
I'm Supergirl.
就像你的堂弟一样
Just like your cousin.
不管我把你打倒多少次
No matter how many times I stamp you out,
你总能奇迹般地复活
you miraculously resurface
穿着一身华丽斗篷  还有完美的发型
with your glossy cape and your perfect hair.
我告诉你一个秘密吧  莱克斯
Let me let you in on a little secret, Lex.
真相和正义必胜
Truth and justice always prevail.
你和你堂弟还真是傻
You and your cousin are such saps.
幸好  我有备而来
Luckily, I came prepared.
我也一样
So did I.
这还多亏了你妹妹
You can thank your sister for this.
瞧  我早说过
See? I told you.
他没法使出足够的能量
He can't put out enough energy.
我帮他就可以
He can, if I help him.
小盒子
Little boxes,
little boxes,
盒子  盒子
boxes and boxes,
子程序  苏格拉底  亚里士多德
and subroutines and Socrates and Aristotle
天神下凡  矩阵  弥撒纪念祈祷文
and Avatar and matrices and Memento
巨蟒剧团
and Monty Python and...
梦想者
Dreamer!
停
Stop...
你快停下
Stop what you're doing!
你这么做没有意义
What you're doing doesn't make any sense!
不
No.
听我说  尼娅
Listen to me, Nia.
不知道你能否听见  但我回来了
I don't know if you can hear me, but I'm back.
我已经调整过来了
I'm realigned, and...
我意识到那一切
And I realize now that everything,
我之前所说的都是错的
everything I said before was wrong.
你能做到的
You can do this.
你就快成功了
You're doing it!
没错
Yes, you did.
就快成功了  看到了吗
You're doing this! You see?
就快成功了  太强了
You're doing it! You're amazing!
简直令人震惊
You're astounding!
你厉害爆了  尼娅·纳尔
You're astazing Nia Nal!
我爱你
And I love you.
系统超载
-搞定他了  -我们赶快出去
- We got him. - All right, let's get out of here!
快走  快走
Let's go, let's go!
赶快出去  快
Get out of here! Let's go!
把这些外星人带去安全的地方
Let's get these aliens somewhere safe.
这样就更好了
That's better.
你个氪星人就笑着迎接我的致命一击吧
Now smile, and take this like a Kryptonian.
不
Oh, no.
No.
你说得对
You were right.
我的艾丽克斯和你的完全不一样
My Alex was nothing like your Alex.
保护你的人民  就像我一样
Protect your people as I protected mine.
这样吧
How about that.
一个外星手铳射二鸟
Two birds, one alien hand-cannon.
这一下是替红色之女报仇
This is for Red Daughter.
都结束了
It's over!
让我拯救你
Let me save you.
拯救
Saved?
被氪星人救
By a Kryptonian?
我宁愿死
I'd rather die.
你不会再有超能力了
No more superpowers for you.
莉娜
Lena.
没想到啊
What a surprise.
我能说什么  莱克斯
What can I say, Lex?
你太好猜了
You've become predictable.
我把日记留给你
I left the journal for you,
还有壁画  希望你能记得这里
paired it with the mural, hoping you would remember this place
在我需要的时候现身
and show up when I needed you.
你明白吗  到头来都是这样  妹妹
You know, it just comes down to this, sis.
只有血亲才是最可靠的
You can only count on blood.
来  帮我一把
Come on, give me a hand.
拜托  莉娜  现在不是演戏的时候
Come on, Lena, this is no time for theatrics.
你我都清楚  无论你多么讨厌我
We both know no matter how much you despise me,
都狠不下心扣扳机
you're not ruthless enough to pull that trigger--
有你在  世界不可能安全
The world will never be a safe place with you in it.
真棒
Oh, brava!
你做到了  莉娜
You did it, Lena.
你杀了我
You killed me.
你终于证明了
You finally proved
一直以来是我低估了你
that I've been underestimating you all this time.
可是  在我死后
But, when I'm gone,
还有谁为你骄傲
who will be left to be proud of you?
你的朋友吗
What, your friends?
被耍的人是你
The joke's on you.
一直都是你
It's always been on you.
你的朋友们从一开始就在骗你
Your friends have been lying to you from the start.
你男朋友吉米
Your boyfriend Jimmy,
艾丽克斯  荣恩
Alex, J'onn,
还有小外星仔布莱尼
that little alien runt Brainy.
连你母亲也是
Even your own mother.
他们嘲笑你  羞辱你
They've mocked you, humiliated you,
背叛你
betrayed you.
每个人都是
Every last one.
逃避事实很管用  对吧
Denial's a very powerful thing, isn't it?
事实一直都摆在你面前
It's been standing right in front of you all this time.
你却选择忽略
And you chose not to see it.
卡拉·丹弗斯就是
Kara Danvers is
超女
Supergirl.
虽然我快死了
I'm about to die,
但至少我活着的时候不是个傻子
but at least I lived without ever being a fool.
你孤家寡人  两手空空
You're left with no one and nothing.
随着凯特科记者卡拉·丹弗斯将事实曝光
Following the revelations of CatCo reporter Kara Danvers' expose,
内阁根据
the Cabinet invoked the
第二十五修正案  罢免贝克的总统职位
25th Amendment to remove Baker from office.
新闻的力量不容小觑
Talk about power of the press.
我受伤的朋友如是说道
Says my injured friend.
我还是不敢相信你的眼睛成了这样
I still can't believe what happened to your eye.
我也是
Me either.
很遗憾布莱尼没能设计出不带副作用的
I'm sorry Brainy couldn't design the Harun-El extractor
哈伦·艾尔提取器  但我们都很高兴你没事
without kickback, but I think we're all just happy you're okay.
我很高兴正义最终获胜
Well, I'm just happy justice prevailed
洛克伍德和他的支持者也被关了起来
and Lockwood and his cohorts got locked up.
这伤也提醒着我  我毕竟是凡人
And the injury reminds me that I'm human,
否则我可能就忘了
which I started to miss.
我很高兴大家又开始交谈了
Well, I'm just happy people are talking again,
开始愿意听取事实
and, you know, listening to facts.
最新消息
莱克斯·卢瑟在雪莱岛爆炸中身亡
对  这些日子太黑暗了
Yeah. These have been some dark days.
我承认  有几次我差点以为
And I'll admit, there were some times where I thought
我们再也没法重见光明
we would never get out of it,
但我们没放弃  依旧不懈努力
but we didn't give up, and we kept chipping away,
直到我们让真相大白
until we brought the truth to light.
你们敢信是新闻业拯救了世界吗
Can you believe the Fourth Estate saved the day?
副总统普拉斯提诺放宽军事管制
Vice President Plastino has lifted martial law
并恢复了《外星人赦免法》
and reinstated the Alien Amnesty Act
直到国会进行全面投票为止
until such time as a full vote can be held in Congress.
另一方面
On another note,
我想给超女捎个信
I want to send a message to Supergirl,
无论她身在何处
wherever she may be.
这个国家曾怀疑你
For a moment, this country doubted you.
但我们不会重蹈覆辙
But we won't make that mistake again.
一个知恩图报的国家感谢你的功劳
A grateful nation thanks you for your service.
城市里没有坦克和士兵就好多了  对吧
City's a lot nicer without the tanks and the soldiers, huh?
话说早了  整年看不见作战背心才算好
If I don't see another tactical vest all year, it'll be too soon.
我们在很短的时间里
We've been through a lot of intense stuff together
一起经历了很多深刻的事  是吧
in a short amount of time, haven't we?
-这将是本世纪最保守的说法  -是的
- That would be the understatement of the century. - Yeah.
奇怪的是
So, here's the strange part.
我不希望它结束
I don't want it to end.
和你的亲密接触
The closeness with you,
让我觉得这是世界上最自然的事情
it has felt like both the most natural thing in the world
就像是一种启示
and like a revelation.
我希望我没有让我们的关系变得尴尬
And I hope to God that I haven't made this awkward between us.
我只是
I just...
我很久没有这种感觉了
I haven't felt like this in a long time,
我只是觉得我必须
and I just felt like I had to--
我也是
Ditto.
不要怕  我们什么都没看见
Fear not. We see nothing.
攻击卡
Attack card.
我就不明白了
I don't understand.
抱歉
Sorry.
你怎么这么快就学会了
How did you get so good at this so quickly?
上次我们玩过后
After last we played,
我回家进行了670亿次模拟
I went home and ran 67 billion simulations.
试图找出最理想的结果
Tried to game out the most desirable outcome.
-所以你是在算牌吗  -没错
- So you're counting cards? - Yes.
她懂了
She gets it.
别告诉别人啊
Don't tell people that.
-欢迎  -你来了
- Hey! - Yay!
她来了
There she is!
詹姆斯很快就到
James will be here soon,
然后全家人就团聚了
and then the whole family will be together.
-好哇  -你去哪里了
- Huzzah! - Where've you been?
我不知道该带什么  所以我红的白的都带了
I didn't know what to bring, so I bought red and white.
-太好了  -真棒
- Yes! - Nice!
既然你来了  我们就能分组玩"你做我猜"
Now that you're here, we can divide up and play Catch Phrase.
是啊  荣恩让我们换掉了平常的队伍
Yeah, J'onn is making us switch up the usual teams.
我的地盘  我说了算
My house, my rules.
但是  你和我是一组的  对吗
But, uh, you're with me, right?
一直如此
Always.
很好
Good.
我再去倒点红酒
I'm gonna get some more wine.
你不会因为布莱尼在游戏里老赢
You're not upset that Brainy's just killing it over there
你就生气吧  因为你知道我们会干掉他
with this game, right? 'Cause you know we're gonna take him down.
-我们会"碾压"他  但是  -对
- Uh, we're gonna cream him, but... - Yeah.
不  我是
No, I'm, uh...
我担心莉娜
I'm worried about Lena.
我必须要告诉她真相
I have to tell her the truth.
我不能再瞒着她了
I can't keep it from her anymore.
莉娜经历了一场劫难
Lena's been through hell.
我们终于能
We finally got to a place
恢复些许正常了
where it sort of feels a little normal again,
所以  我也说不清  在我们夺走这一切之前
so, I don't know, maybe you just let her enjoy the evening
你就让她好好享受今晚吧
before we take it away.
你说的没错
You're right.
今晚不说
Not tonight.
快快快  好了  我们开始
Come on, come on, come on. Okay, here we go.
相互对立只会导致更多的分裂
Turning against each other has only led to more division,
更多的仇恨和暴力
more hate and more violence.
一定有更好的办法
There must be a better way.
你的观点因为你父亲的事而改变了吗
Has your perspective changed because of what happened to your father?
是的
Yes.
我亲眼目睹了
I've seen firsthand how
这种愤怒是如何撕裂一个家庭的
that kind of anger can tear a family apart.
我有那种心碎的经历
I've lived that heartbreak.
我想确保没有人会再经历这种事
And I wanna make sure nobody else has to.
如果人类和外星人能彼此倾听
If humans and aliens can just listen to each other,
那我们就能站起来  团结起来
then we can stand up, united,
对付那些企图分裂我们的人
against those who seek to divide us.
在休假吗
Vacation?
周末旅行
Weekend trip.
看来你收拾了不少东西啊
Looks like you packed plenty.
但我们会找到你的  伊芙
But we'll always find you, Eve.
不管你戴了多少假发
No matter how many wigs you cycle through.
你是谁
Who are you?
你心知肚明  亲爱的
You already know that, dear.
我照你说的做了
I did everything you asked.
我为他工作
I worked for him.
我为了他而伤害人们
I hurt people for him.
莱克斯应该有所成就的
Lex was supposed to move the needle.
他失败了
He failed.
那你就放过我吧
So let me go.
抱歉  亲爱的
Sorry, sweetie,
那不在议程上
that's not on the agenda.
利维坦无处不在
Leviathan is everywhere.
每个人都是利维坦
Leviathan is everyone.
利维坦要来了
And Leviathan is coming.
我在哪里
Where am I?
地球
Earth.
不可能
It can't be.
你被困已久
You've been trapped for too long.
都是你人民的一个幻影
A phantom to your people.
现在是时候
Now it is time to avenge
向那些辜负你的弟兄们报仇了
yourself against the brother who wronged you.
你会帮助我吗
Will you help me?
我已经把你带到了这里
It was I that brought you here.
你必须自己走这条路
You must walk the path yourself.
再说了
Besides,
我还要去一个地方
I have one more place to visit.
我来找你了  荣恩·荣兹